Okay, so before even if I go into the daily routine problems and whatever, all these kinds
of things, what I want specifically is to make sure that whatever I'm saying, you can
understand and reply to me and automate that, right?
But the problem is that what I'm seeing right now is that you say that you automatically
transcribe and prompt me back.
But so far, for the past few messages, you have transcribed it very fast, after I prompt
you.
So the problem is that I need to prompt you.
Is there a way that I could fix something like, once again, is that a cron job, is that
a heartbeat, is it something that I need to install, a skill I need to install that can
just double check with you or prompt you back after I send a voice message to transcribe
or something?