I would say let's do this in three levels okay so for example one if this transcription is great
which is what I'm seeing right in front of me you are you are saying that uh even though there's a
huge fan in the background there's a lot blowing and everything you can still understand me and
you are transcribing it correctly and the items and everything makes sense to you
that's level one means that okay you can understand quite fast it makes sense to you go ahead with
things right level two will be things like if I mention names or products services things that
seem to be easily mistranslated for example when I was talking about Claude bot which is you they
would usually it will be translated into anthropic cloud right or uh talk about open claw some people
hear it as something else right so that's where this level two where sometimes the transcription
could mix up um I want you to be able to figure out how to understand what I'm actually saying
first and if it's a mistake then you can ask for clarification right now level three is where
I guess it's just really it doesn't make sense to you about what I'm asking for
and then yeah just let me know how I can help you to fix that